Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Records 5953
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records
1969-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5953
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Records, arbitation decisions.
5743711
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 22, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 04, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Seidenberg, Jacob.
5743711
- Union Pacific; Southern Pacific; Unocal Chemical; Overseas Education Association (Germany Region); Bugle Rental; Baker and Confectionary Funds (OPEIU); Erwin Mills; G. Heileman Brewing; Burlington Northern (Box 1)
  - Southern Pacific Transportation Company - Investigations (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    1
  - Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 1, Folder 3)
    2
  - Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 1, Folder 4)
    3
  - Union Pacific Railroad company (Box 1, Folder 5)
    4
  - UNOCOL - Chemical Division IBT Local 311 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - DOD (DOS) - OEA FMCS Germany (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bugle Rental Service Local 570 - IBT (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BCW / Health Benefits & Pension funds Health + Welfare Local 2 - OPEIU (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Erwin Mills ACTWU Local 2507 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - G Heileman Brewery Co. Brewery worker - L 1010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - PL 5155 SP - UTU (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - IBEWU - OPIEU (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - P.L. board No 5007 BN - BLE (Box 1, Folder 14)
- St. Louis Southwestern RR; Hubbell Inc.; Giant Foods; Boston and Maine Corp. (Box 2)
  - Before Administration Board No. 387 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Employee's Exhibit No. V1 + V3 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Employee's Exhibit No. V1 Maine Central railroad Company Portland Terminal company Schedule of Rules Governing Rates of Pay and Working Conditions of train and Yard Service Employees Effective July 1, 1969; Collective Agreements between Canadian Pacific Limited and United Transportation Union on behalf of the Conductors, Baggagemen, trainmen, Yardmen, Switchtenders, Yardmasters employed on the Brownville, Maine and Newport, Vermont Seniority Rosters Reprinted November 1, 1974
  - Memorandum of Agreement; Boston and Maine Corporation, Average Annual 1978 Wage for employees in Domestic Industries (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Before Board of Arbitration No. 387 Statement (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Giant Food Inc. and United Food & commercial Workers, Local 400; June 28, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Giant of Landover, Inc. Appellant (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Giant food Inc. -- UFCW Local 400 Discharge (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Giant food - UFCW Local 400 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hubbell Lighting FMCS (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Agreements (Box 2, Folder 10)
- CSX Transportation Inc. (former Balt & Ohio RR); Columbia Typographical/USGPO: Agency Fee Challengers (Box 3)
  - Public Law Board No. 4833 UTU vs CSX Transportation Inc. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Award No 37 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - employees' Submission to Public Law board 4833 PLB Docket 223 UTU vs CSX Transportation (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Public Law Board No. 4833 UTU vs CSX Transportation (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Submission to Public Law Board No. 4833 Dockets 225 and 226 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Employees' Submission to Public Law Board 4833 Docket 222 UTU and CSX Transportation (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Government Printing Office and Columbia Typographical Union 101-12, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Public Law board No. 4833 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GPO - ITU - Local 101-12 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - AAA CWA Agency Fee Challenges, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CWA, AFL-CIO, Union and Agency Fee challenges, Apellants June 30, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CWA, AFL-CIO, Union + Agency Fee challenges, Appellants, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - CWA, AFL-CIO, Union Agency Fee Challenges, Appellants, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - PLB 4833 UTU vs CSX (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Patapsco & Back River RR Co.; Norfolk Southern; Lower Lake Dock Co.; Washington Gas Light Co.; Yellow Freight System; Amtrak; Entenmann's; Winner Distributing; Philadelphia Gas Works; B. Green & Co.; Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 4)
  - Allen Fords - IBT - L356 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - PLB 4762 AMTRAK - TCU (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - General Foam Plastic - IWAL - 75 FMCS 90 + 17065 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - SP Seminar Mock Arbitration (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Report of Panel on Impasse of Negotiations on the 1991-1992 Contract Between the Board of Education of Anne Arundel County and Secretaries and Assistants Association of Anne Arundel County (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - UPIU, Local No. 1925 and MacMillan Bloedel, Inc. Jacob Seidenberg, Esquire Aug 2, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Board No 513 CSX Transportation Co - UTU (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - International Union of Gas Workers and Washington Gas Light Company Grievance March 31, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Bank Stationary Co. Baltimore Typographical Union (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - PLB No. 4229 UP - UTU (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - EAL - TWU Local 553 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - B Green + Co. - IBT Local 570 FMCS No. 89 - 24830 Grievance (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission NTEU No. 12 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Phila Glass works - Gas Workers Employee Union AAA (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - AFA and Braniff Airways, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - PL 4770 AMTRAK - BLE (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Entenmann's Bakery Warehouse Employees local 570 FMCS No.: 89-20798 Issue: change of pay practice January 18, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - AAA Case No. 14 300 1572 89 Q The Winner Distributing Company and Brewery Workers Union Local 1010 Our File No. 7893-14 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Yellow Freight Co - Local 551 Panel (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - WGl - IUGW (discharge) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - PLB No. 4869 Lower Lake Dock Co. & ILA (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - PLB No. 4807 (Procedural): Southern Railway Company and American Train Dispatchers Association (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - PLB 4895 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Blue Diamond Co.; St. Louis Southwestern; Penn Central Transportation Co.; Atchison Topeka & Santa Fe; US Air; Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority (Box 5)
  - Agreement between the St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company and the United Transportation Union (CT&Y) Covering Rates of Pay and Working Conditions for Trainmen & Yardmen (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - PLB No. 1296 UTU vs. Robert Blanchette, Richard C. Bond and John H. McArthur, Trustees of The Property of Penn Central Transportation company, Debtor docket No. 1 Carrier's Brief (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rail Act of 1980 Background Materials prepared for the use of the Committee on interstate and foreign Commerce House of Representatives and its Subcommittee on Transportation and commerce Ninety- Sixth Congress Second Session May 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Black Diamond - Teamster Local 557docket No. 08-30-93 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - PLB No. 1367 Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers vs. The Atchison, topeka and Santa Fe Railway company - coast lines (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - UTU - Local 1594 - SEPA AAA (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ganas Discipline Grievance/System Board Joint Exhibits (Box 5, Folder 7)
- VanNess East; General Services Administration; RCA Borinquen; Pan Am; Southland Industries; Brhd. Of Locomotive Engineers; B.F. Goodrich; National RR Passenger Corp.; Maine Central RR; Allis Chalmers; Benjamin Obdyke Co.; Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe; St (Box 6)
  - RCA - IBEWU - Local 2296 FMCS 83K (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - GSA - AFGE Suspension (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Van Ness East - SEIU Local 82 FMCS (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Southland industries AAA (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - PANAM Flight Engineers TWU (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - B.F. Goodrich - UPIU - Local 1449 FMCS No. 87 - 13964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - ARB No. 476 BLE - EJ & E (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - RCA Corporation and Association of Scientists and Professional engineering Personnel (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - PL 4435 AMTRAK - IAMAW Procedural (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - IAMAW and Allis-Chalmers corporation (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Warehouse Employees union 169 AAA (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees snf Maine Central Railroad Company (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - PLB No. 4214 Santa Fe - BLE (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - UTU vs. St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - UTU vs St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Carrier's file: [TRN D92-43 20983, YDMD 92-1, TRN D92-16]
- CSX Transportation; Union Pacific; Maine Central RR; St. Louis Southwestern RR; Southern Pacific; Long Island RR (Box 7)
  - UTU vs. CSX Case and Docket No. 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - UTU vs. CSX Case and Docket No. 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - UTU vs. CSX Case + docket No. 5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Maine Central Railroad Company (1) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Appearances of William E. LaRue, Vice President; John J. Davison, General Chairman
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Maine Central Railroad Company (2) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Case No. 1
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Maine Central Railroad Company (3) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Case No. 2
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees and Maine Central Railroad Company Other submissions (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Exhibits
  - PLB No. 5315 docket No. 2, 2a Case No. 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Appendix "A" Section 11 Arbitration Mendocino coast Conditions (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Union Pacific Railroad Company PLB No. 3742 case No. 23 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - PLB No. 3742 Case No. 20 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - PLB No. 3742 Case No. 21 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - LIRR - BRAC (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PLB No. 4948 St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company UTU (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Washington Gas Light Co.; American Airlines; Indiana Hi-Rail Corp.; Philadelphia Gas Works; Conrail; Norfolk Southern; CSX Transportation; American Fed. Of Teachers Staff Union; Southern Pacific; GNB Inc.; Rite Aid Corp.; Long Island RR Co.; Claire Frock (Box 8)
  - WGL - IUGW (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - EAL - TWU Local 553 Case No. 690-86 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - CLB Trucking co. Local 557 - IBT Grievance (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SBA #1014 US - BRC (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Formosa Plastics UPIU -L 1134 AAA (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - N + W - Southern RR IAMAW (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - GSA - Nat'l Capital Region AFGE - Local 1733 Council 236 (Grievance) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - EAL - TWU - Local 553 Case No. 76-87 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - EAL - TWU -Local 553 Case No. 91-87 (Grievance) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - CSX - UTU (Connesville, PA) New York Dock (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - EAL - TWU - Local 553Case No. 77-87 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - PLB No. 4382 council UTU (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - B Green Co. Inc. - IAMAW Lodge 186 FMCS Case No. 88 Discharge (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - D. C. School Board AFSCME - Local 2093 Termination (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Clare Frocks - ILGWU (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Proceedings LIRR-BLE (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Rite Aid Corp. - Metro Guild of Pharmacists l-660R-UFCW (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - GNP Inc. - IBEWU -Local 2217 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - PL Board No. 4463 SP - BLE (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - American Fed. Of Teachers - AFT Action AAA (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - CSX - UTU - Protective Condition (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - CSX - UTU Parkersburg Russell, KY New York Dock (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - NW + DMU Railroad (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - PLB No. 4188 Conrail - URSA Vol. II (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Philadelphia Gas Workers - Gas Worker union - Local 686 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - PLB 4681 Indiana Hi-Rail UTU (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - AAA - ALA AAPA Board of Adjustment (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - WGL - IUGW (Box 8, Folder 28)
- DC Board of Education; Boston & Maine Corp. (Box 9)
  - D.C. Board of Education (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Boston and Maine Corporation, Debtor and UTU, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chicago, West Pullman & Southern Railroad & UTU (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - DC Board of Ed and Teachers Union (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Boston and Maine Corporation, Debtor and UTU (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board of Arbitration No. 387 Employee's Submission; Boston and Maine Corporation and UTU (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Boston and Maine Corporation and UTU (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Boston and Maine - UTU; Statement of Robert Lieb; 1971 Reorganization Plan (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Boston and Maine - UTU; Statement of Robert Lieb; 1971 Reorganization Plan (Box 9, Folder 8)